fukitol.com 2012-06-10

# PRIVACY POLICY | When Life Just Blows...FUKITOL! | LEGAL

### **PRIVACY POLICY**

This site is operated by FUKITOL, Inc. Our Privacy Policy is designed to tell you about the policies that govern our collection, use, and disclosure of the information that you may provide via our Websites.  **Before using or submitting information to this site, please read this entire Private Policy. Please be aware that this Privacy Policy generally describes FUKITOL, Inc. sites, although the particular site you are viewing may not include all the items described.**  This site is governed solely by applicable Federal and State laws and governmental regulations in the United States and Canada. Use of this site constitutes your consent to application of such laws and regulations and to our Privacy Policy. 

 **Information Use and Disclosure**

 **** Your name, address, e-mail address, and any other personally identifiable information you provide may be used by FUKITOL, Inc., its business partners and consultants to provide you with information about FUKITOL products, and/or services. FUKITOL, Inc. will not sell or rent the personally identifiable information collected via this site to a third party. We reserve the right to disclose information to respond to duly authorized information requests of governmental authorities or where required by law.   

You can notify FUKITOL that you wish to discontinue receiving information at any time (see  **How To Contact Us**  below).

By using this site, you agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy. Whenever you submit information via this site, you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We may use your information to improve the value of our site's content, to present the site in a fashion customized to match your preferences, to supply information to you (if you requested it), for research and marketing purposes, and for the purposes specified in this Privacy Policy.

We may combine personally identifiable information with other actively collected information unless we specify otherwise at the point of collection. FUKITOL will take reasonable measure to prevent passively collected information from being combined with personally identifiable information, unless you consent otherwise.

We will also make full use of all information acquired through this site that is not personally identifiable.

 **Access and Updates**

To keep your personally identifiable information accurate, current, and complete, please contact us as specified below. We will take reasonable steps to update or correct personally identifiable information in our possession that you have previously submitted via this site.

 **Security**

Please bear in mind that no Internet transmission is ever 100% secure or error-free. More specifically, e-mail sent to or from this site may not be secure. As a result, you should take particular care in deciding what information you send via e-mail. Any passwords, ID numbers, or other special access numbers you might use to access any part of this site are your responsibility; take care to safeguard them. FUKITOL takes reasonable steps to protect your personally identifiable information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

 **Links to Other Websites**

Links or references to other Websites may appear within this site. We do not control these Websites. You should be aware that this Privacy Policy does not apply to any Websites other than those operated by FUKITOL, Inc. Visitors to other Websites are encouraged to read their privacy policies before exploring them.

 **About Children**

Children under the age of 18 are not the intended audience for this site. We will not knowingly collect information from site visitors in this age group. We encourage parents to be aware of their children's use of the Internet and discuss what kind of information they are allowed to disclose to Websites. 

 **Active Information Collection**

This site may actively collect information from its visitors both by asking them specific questions and by facilitating direct communications with us via e-mail, feedback forms, etc. Some of the information that visitors submit may be personally identifiable information (this is, information that can be uniquely identified with an individual, such as full name, address, e-mail address, phone number, and so on). 

In some cases we might collect nonpersonally identifiable information that you elect to provide voluntarily, such as gender or zip code.

This site may also offer some features and activities (such as newsletter subscriptions, downloads, etc.) which may require you to submit information in order to receive or benefit from them. You will be informed at each information collection point what information is required and what information is optional.

 **Passive Information Collection**

Like many other websites, this site may also collect some information passively as you navigate through the site (that is, this information is gathered without your actively providing the information), using various technologies and means, such as navigational data collection.

 **Navigational data**  ("log files," "server logs," and "clickstream" data) are used for system management, to improve the content of the site, market research purposes, and to communicate information to visitors. This site may or may not use navigational data.

One of the ways information may be passively collected is by the use of Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. An IP address is a number assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider so you can access the Internet. IP addresses are generally considered to be nonpersonally identifiable information, because most IP addresses are dynamic (they change each time you connect to the Internet), rather than static (unique to any one particular user's computer). We may use your IP address to improve or administer the site, diagnose server problems, report aggregate information, or to determine the fastest connection route between your computer and our site.

Another method for passive information collection is by means of "cookies." A "cookie" is a small data text file, which a Website stores on your computer's hard drive (if your Web browser permits) that can later be retrieved to identify you. "Session cookies" are temporary bits of information that are erased once you exit your Web browser window or otherwise turn your computer off. Session cookies are used to improve navigation on Websites and to collect aggregate statistical information.

This site may use both cookies and session cookies. If you do not wish to receive cookies from this or any other site, you can change your computer's settings so that it will no longer accept cookies.

 **Turning off cookies.**  Be aware that in some cases, you need to accept cookies from a site to take full advantage of its services. This is especially true on sites that require a user ID or a password.

In Internet Explorer 4, go to the "View" menu and select "Options." In the "Options" dialog box, click the "Advanced" tab. Scroll down the list box and deselect the "Always Accept Cookies" option. You may select "Prompt Before Accepting Cookies" if you would like to selectively accept them.

In Internet Explorer 5, go to the "Tools" menu and select "Internet Options." Choose the "Security" tab and click on the "Custom Level" box. Scroll down to "Cookies" and change your options.

In Internet Explorer 6, go to the "Tools" menu and select "Internet Options." Choose the "Privacy" tab to control your cookie options. You may turn off all cookies by setting your privacy level to "Block All Cookies," or specify that you want to block cookies only from a particular Website by selecting the "Websites / Edit..." button.

In Netscape Navigator, select "Preferences" from the "Edit" menu, then choose "Advanced." Either select "Disable Cookies" or check "Warn Me Before Accepting a Cookie."

 **Internet tags**  (also known as single-pixel GIFs, clear GIFs, invisible GIFs, and 1-by-1 GIFs) are smaller than cookies and tell the Web site server information such as the IP address and browser type related to the visitor's computer. This site may or may not use Internet tags.

 **How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Privacy Policy or the information collection practices of this site, please contact us at: 

FUKITOL  
125 - 1216 Alpha Lake Road  
Whistler, British Columbia  
V0N 1B1 

Phone: 1-888-FUK1TOL   
Fax: 1-888-FUK1TOL   
Email:  [Info@FUKITOL.com](mailto:Info@FUKITOL.com)

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

FUKITOL, Inc. reserves the right to modify, add or remove portions of this privacy policy at its discretion. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted on this site. Please check back periodically, and especially before you provide any personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy was last updated on January 21, 2004.

 **Other Terms**

Your use of this site is subject to our Legal Notice.
